bbamantra.com 2019-01-21

# Privacy Policy - BBA|mantra

We respect the privacy of our users and assure them their personal details and other information shared will always be protected. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by BBA|mantra and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, BBA|mantra makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

BBA|mantra uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on bbamantra.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to bbamantra.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on BBA|mantra send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

BBA|mantra has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. BBA|mantra’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browser’s respective websites.

In order to avail the services of [bbamantra.com](https://www.bbamantra.com/), users are required to provide certain information for the registration purposes like: name and e-mail.

The information given enables us to further update our website with an aim to provide the most user-friendly services.

Here we may like to mention that to improve the responsiveness of the websites for the users we may use cookies, or similar electronic tools to collect information. This information will be used to assign each visitor a unique, random number to understand the user’s individual interests using the identified computer.

When you register with us, we will contact you from time to time for updating of your content to provide the users such features that we believe may benefit them. We use the information like IP address to deliver our web pages to you on your request, to tailor our site to your interests, to measure traffic to our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors are based.

It would be pertinent to inform that we usually share information to our advertisers to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website. It is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site.

We use third-party advertising companies to display ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your visits to this website and other websites to provide advertisements about goods and services of your interest.

All information gathered on the site is securely stored within a controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall. The access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited.

However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. So even though we may promise to keep your information confidential, we cannot be accountable for any lapses on which we have no control.

Further, internet is a dynamic and evolving medium, and to incorporate necessary future changes we may be changing our privacy policy from time to time. However, any information collected from you will always be consistent with our privacy policy, regardless of the future changes.

If you have questions, queries or clarifications with respect to our privacy policy, please send your concern at:  [contact@bbamantra.com](mailto:contact@bbamantra.com)

Or send postal mail addressed to:

Block-A, Top Floor, Arif Apartment,

New Hyderabd, Lucknow – 226007

Phone: +918874221122
